Evens wins!
Ooh!
Looks like Lady Luck's
taking a liking to you!
Ain't that sweet?
You're really something else!
Not everyone can hit a
winning streak that grand!
For you.
That's for the sushi,
thanks for covering me.
Oh, I think you ended me a
bit too much there, chief.
I'll win some more, don't you worry.
Man,
to think we were just
looking for shelter from the
rain—I got a good feeling
if I stick to your side;
I'll never go hungry, mister.
You might be the finest man in water.
water
Ugh, sake is going to taste
extra special tonight.
Place your bets.
Odds. Wow!
You said that was such
a beam of confidence.
Gave me chills.
Anyone else?
Last call, then.
Calling it!
It's odds!
Thought you had that one.
No sword style.
Tatsumaki!
Oh, looks like we caught a rat!
You guys are so Uncle.
Get the sky! Hurry up!
Hm.
Free punching bags as well?
This place has everything.
Don't hold back. Take him down!
One Sword Style.
Great Dragon Shock!
Whoa, one sec, mister, I'm a firm
believer in good old balance.
Good and evil, black and
white, odds and evens.
You really got them good,
so let's call it a day.
Yeah.
I have a complaint for the manager.
And if I'm not mistaken,
that would be you, is it not?
Here, take it!
Just get the hell out of
here and don't come back!
One dream, one wish.
If you want it, gotta go over the top.
Setting sail and heading for the unknown.
Cutting through the
winds and waves as I go.
Gotta keep it up, never stopping, no?
Cause I'm aiming to get there first, yeah.
It's all or nothing, no time to worry.
Do it later, right now I'm living free.
When your foes look like
they will overwhelm you.
It means your heart's saying
this is what you can't do.
Despite all that to run is not an option.
Once they're close to
feel the satisfaction.
You think I'm rude,
here's my appreciation.
When things are getting
tough, just gotta smile.
If you are going on your way.
And you're looking for
a fresh, brand new day.
Then make sure your only
thought you have is.
Yes, I can.
As you're on your way.
Marked maps will be made.
Yes, with every step that you will take.
Just look at all you've been through.
Look ahead on new horizons in view.
Shining brightly, oh, who
knows what's waiting for you?
Dream living, that's the way.
Make like a hurricane.
Now, got to make your mark today.
One dream, one wish.
Your dreams don't run away.
Go for the knockout!
Over the top!
Man, oh man, I was shaking
like a leaf. What about you?
Could you shut up for a sec?
Why, that's a mighty kind suggestion,
my friend, and very perceptive.
Seeing as I've been running my mouth so
much, my throat could do with a bit of rest.
But more importantly, I realize I
haven't properly introduced myself.
The name's Turner Yasuie, but
everyone calls me Seek-a-Fit Yasuie.
Nice to meet you.
Wow.
Even when you don't speak,
your mug says it all.
What a hunk, what a stud.
Why, I bet you can't
keep the ladies off you.
Why are you following me?
I got this really strong feeling
while we were at the gambling house.
That if I stepped by your side, then the
world would be all sunshine and rainbows.
I should have measured this back there.
But not everyone stands up for those guys.
They're underlings of the Kyoshiro family.
Ayaka's a group from the
capital, real dreadful lowlifes.
Know what I mean?
Man, I'm telling you.
If I were a woman, your heroics
would have me weak in the knees.
You see something ahead, mister?
I think I recognize that place. Woo-hoo!
I'm sure you do.
That'd be the flower capital.
And that settlement in front of it?
None other than Okobore, or more officially
Ebisu, which is also my hometown.
Your home sounds wealthy.
Ebisu's the god of good fortune.
There's a reason it has that name.
But you'll just have to wait and see.
All right.
Who's next?
I'll take one bowl of Sabo. But of course.
That guy, who is he?
Beats me, but he sure draws a crowd.
Arrogant little playboy.
He has no clue whose
turf he's muscled it on.
That's all right.
We'll teach him.
Beat that iron!
Hold that stone!
It's fine if you can't work,
but at least have the decency
to die and get out of the way!
This is all?
I told you the rules.
All five blocks get one millet dumpling.
Is old man yo too frail to
earn his own food anymore?
What a shame.
you've stuck around long
enough time to kick the bucket I
worked so hard all day long huh
you got something to say the next
time you talk back to a guard
I'll take one of your limbs off
next don't fight back you gotta
save your energy you old man, yo,
or you're going to end up dead.
Wow.
Four exchange tickets, huh?
Someone's a hard worker.
Here I come.
Move it, you damn morons.
I'll run you over!
What's it, Jaggy?
I'm right here!
Then how about I run you over, too?
No!
Whoa, hold on. We're full.
You've brought us enough for today.
Full!
Then you should bring another ship!
Quit slacking off!
Sorry, sir!
So, how many stones did those two haul?
I lost count at 500 or so.
Huh?
Then they're handcuffs?
Sea prism stones.
So that's with their power drained!
I don't even want to think about what
they can do if they got those figs off!
I did my work!
Now work over the food!
Oh! What?!
Damn, that's a lot of food.
Never seen anyone pull that off.
Got a problem?
Yeah, you dumb face.
I made one more trip than
you, you know. So what?
I was still faster.
No, you weren't.
I'm the strongest and the fastest.
How do you know how many rocks you hauled?
You can't even count.
I can't, too.
My ass, you can.
Wait a sec.
Weren't they beat up real
bad when they came here?
I mean,
it must have been the
food that healed them
because it sure as hell
wasn't the slave labor,
right?
That's not how the human body works.
How are we supposed to break their
spirits when they're like this?
Hey, say something to them.
Hmm?
Oh.
Don't chew too fast. What?
Are you there, Mom?
My food!
It's gone!
Who did this?
My food is all gone!
They took every last bite!
Somebody here's sleeping on the job!
This will not end well.
Stop hiding and confess already!
Please, someone help!
Oh, man, you were strapped!
You gotta keep crawling!
General Tobon!
The perpetrators are
behind bars. Well, good.
And the dumplings?
They already ate it all.
And you two just stood there
and watched while they did it.
The thing is, they worked super hard
and got paid the correct amount of food.
So what are we going to say?
No.
I'm the vice warden here,
and I will stand for you.
I can't understand it once
the hippo closes its mouth.
Dobon, sir.
I said, bring them here!
They'll suffer for this!
All right, sir, here
are the culprits. Huh?
Teach them a lesson.
Let's go!
I never thought I see a prisoner
with a belly full of food.
I wish that was me!
Listen, punks, I'm obviously a big eater,
but you only left me three dumplings.
How is that enough?
I've got two mouths to feed. Look at me.
You think this is a joke?
Hold on a sec.
I got to digest here.
What the hell is that supposed to mean?
You prisoners wiped that
stupid grin off your face.
My precious Fight!
Hey!
Wouldn't push my luck if I were you.
Maybe you haven't heard, but there's a
rule if you mess with the guards here.
Your arms will be cut off
for the first offense.
And for the second, your legs.
As for the third, you'll
be sentenced to death.
So watch yourself!
Got that, newbies?
There's no room for defiance against me
Listen,
you took our powers away with these cuffs
and we still hold that stone for you.
You gonna punish us for
working our asses off?
Get this through your thick heads, morons!
The reason I'm punishing you
is because you ate all my food!
All right, fine!
Jaggy.
Yibbles!
It's time for you to play!
Poor babies!
It's like a torture shaver inside there!
Just wait for the screams!
What the hell happened?
I've never seen the
hippo go down like this.
Vice Warden, are you okay?
You're in for it now!
You will get the death penalty for sure!
It wasn't us. What?
If you think that we did
something wrong, proof it.
Hell yeah!
Tell those jerks!
You are my hero!
Fresh and ready, get your Sabo today!
You don't want to miss it!
Sandoros Special, the best Sabo in town!
Do it to me now!
Here you go, ladies.
Thanks for waiting.
Wow, now that is insanely good.
Any update on Luffy?
If he broke out of that labor camp,
we'd probably hear the news, right?
Then again, it's pretty far away.
Anyhow, I'm sure he'll be freeing
plenty of time for the raid.
I'm glad you made it out
of that mess safe, Sanji.
Because now I get to enjoy your food.
I don't care if you enjoy it or not.
Otterbee?
Is it yummy?
Yummy.
Why, it's exquisite.
You want to see exquisite,
then look in the mirror, baby!
One problem.
The silver's good and all, but it's
only attracting a bunch of girls.
You gotta cook something spicy that
samurai can knock back with sake.
Don't make that face!
We're trying to recruit allies, dumbass!
Hey, Franky, look.
Here come some guys now.
Pardon.
Excuse us.
Coming through, ladies.
This won't take long.
Hey, we've been waiting for ages.
Don't cut in line.
Oh, what a pity.
I don't care.
It's the Kyoshiro family.
Move it, you little runt.
doing good business huh very
impressive uh-huh sure can't complain
your fellows are customers right
if you want to eat then you gotta
wait in line no thanks we just
have a quick question who gave you
permission to set up shop here
because i sure didn't get the memo
we're the kyoshiro family and this
here is our turf either you pay
us our or we're gonna shove that
sober where the sun don't shine.
Eh, I think I'll pass.
How interesting.
Why are they here?
Are you saying you know
these guys? Uh-huh.
The other day, I performed at a banquet
hall owned by a man named Kyoshiro.
Shogun Orochi is truly a gutless wonder.
Liquor?
I require more liquor.
He was a samurai, loud
and arrogant as they come.
It seems he's the boss of a Yakuza group.
I haven't seen them before, but
these men are likely his underlings.
Maybe I didn't make myself clear.
You gotta pay up and you gotta do it now!
Why's that?
Because you need us.
Who else is gonna protect you if
someone attacks your little shop?
If that's all, then I'll be fine.
I'm pretty freakin strong here.
Thanks for waiting little lady
Okay,
did you think you're
such a tough guy fight
me see if you can protect your little shop
It looks so yummy! Hey, Brat! Huh?
This shop's closing down!
Don't eat that!
I can't tell if that guy made
her laugh or cry. We're kidding.
My sofa!
What, jeez?
Nothing pisses off Sanji more than that.
Go home already.
The shop's closed, you dear.
Buzz off!
The pity buddy's fresh out of sober.
Can you hurry it up, ladies?
Because we ain't gone all day.
I, uh, maybe we better move.
Hey!
You need something?
Yeah, I need you to finish your food.
All of it.
You picking a fight?
Seriously?
Hey, Suke! Kaku! Right here!
Let's put him in this place!
Oh, yeah!
You bastard!
You
bastard!
D-Damn it!
Die! Me!
What did you do?
Why is that Zeff guy so strong?
I don't know, but I think I'm in love.
Sorry, man.
I'm not gonna let you hog all the fuck.
Here we go!
Leave your hands off of me!
What's wrong with you?
Franosuke Iron!
SUFLEX BABY!!!
He's strong too, I guess,
but isn't this really bad?
Now open wide.
You're going to eat every part.
Nobody's wasted food on my watch. Get it?
People wait in line for this all day.
What's wrong?
You want some, too?
You aren't my words, damn it.
Come on, up there you go, big boy.
What a generous tip.
I had a feeling it would end up like that,
but you think they'll let
us get away with this?
Maybe you're right, Usopp.
It had a catastrophic effect on business.
We had a line all the way down the
street, and now it's completely empty.
Looks like the perfect
scene for a showdown.
Now I'm getting nervous.
It's that girl who had her
Sabo thrown on the street.
I can't figure her out.
She's always laughing or crying or both.
Uh, hold on.
What is it?
I think I've seen her
somewhere before, actually.
Now that's a haul.
Usohachi, you really cleaned up today.
Guess I sold more than I realized, huh?
Hm?
You need something, kid?
So this medicine, it fixes
anything, right? Yeah.
It stops bleeding and stops all pain.
It's my miracle toad oil.
Makes your problems disappear.
Ah!
That's wonderful!
I think I saw her at the shrine.
Sorry about that I hate to
have to leave you without
your sofa thankfully there
was some left here eat up
Oh, boy!
It's so good!
Seeing your smile is making me smile, too.
Well, fancy that!
I heard about how awesome your Sabo was,
so I knew I had to get
somewhere I'd go crazy.
But then I saw that line,
Whoa, Bonnie, that was big!
It was an even bigger line than you had
for your toad oil, and that does miracles!
It sure does.
The point of the story is, I was in
line so long that I'm late for work!
Late for work?
You're working a job, kiddo? Yep!
I worked extra hard to
save money because I
wanted to try out the
fancy Sabo no matter what!
But then it got knocked over.
That was sad!
But it worked out, so I'm happy now.
Well, that's great.
A lovely ending, huh?
Thanks, kid.
By the way, I didn't catch your name.
My name's Dock, but say
it with an O in front.
Right. So...
So, Otoko? I guess.
That's what this says.
Otoko means boy, but I'm not a boy.
Don't you get the joke?
I'm a girl!
Isn't that funny?
I'm not a boy!
Well, at least it's
easy to remember, right?
Yeah, I won't be forgetting that!
It's a great name.
Yeah, it is.
Wow, that was worth it.
Thanks a bunch. Of course.
You come back again, okay?
I forgot.
I'm very late for work.
Like super late.
That reminds me.
I'll be passing through here later today.
It's the Oran's procession
after all. Oran?
Dock, are you a Gomorrah by any chance?
I am, so I gotta run!
The procession's already starting!
Bye, I'll see you! Thanks again!
The Oran's really pretty,
so don't miss out!
Bye, Dock!
Man, she's great.
Really makes you smile.
She is precious, isn't she? And funny.
I finally get a peek at the famous
oiron, this is a dream come true!
What's an oiron?
What's a comodo?
I'll tell you!
It's a wrinkled-up paper
lantern come to life!
You're here, too?
Who you calling a paper lantern, huh?
I'll bring a hole in your
hide, you little snot!
You don't know about our Oden?
What do you live under a rock?
She's a superstar.
Go on, go on.
There's only one Oden in all of Wano,
and this legend's name is Komurasaki.
Longed for by men, a role model for women,
Sheer sophistication, a beauty that
could upturn the whole country.
She is a woman envied by heaven itself,
Both pure and noble, that's Komurasaki!
Impossible!
A woman like that doesn't exist!
You'll find out for yourself soon enough!
Do you hear that?
The time is at hand!
The cheers swell to a mighty roar as
the sound of music marks her coming!
The Ordon's procession is
on its way to Orochi Castle.
She will be making an appearance
at the Shogun's banquet.
The girl you spoke to is a Gomorrah, a
child attendant who goes with the Oiran.
Ah, so that's what those words mean.
Oh, Oroby, I have good news.
Straight from the flower capital, no less.
What is it?
Congratulations!
You've been summoned to the
castle for the banquet today.
Wasn't that your dream?
To meet Shogun Orochi in person? Yes.
Yeah!
I knew you could pull it off!
Now let's get home and get
you ready! Yes, ma 'am.
I can hardly wait.
Hey, Straw Hat Guy, you're
really something else.
What clan are you from?
You really put on one hell of a show.
Every prisoner I've seen today
won't stop talking about you.
Leave me alone.
Don't be like that.
You're our hero.
That was the only fun
we've had in forever.
Guy's kind of a jerk.
Mr. Straw Hats.
Thank you so much for saving my
useless hide in your battle yesterday.
Though it's a dead, I could
never hope to pay back.
I had to beat him anyway. It's no biggie.
Here.
Take these.
Can't work on an empty stomach, right?
Why, I couldn't possibly
accept such a thing.
I'm just a good-for-nothing,
undeserving of such kindness.
Come on, just take it. You're funny.
Well, see you later.
I vow to use it wisely.
Thank you sincerely.
Thank you sincerely. What a weirdo.
Sir Luffy.
Race, what's up?
Please pardon the wait.
I have located the key to your
handcuffs, but I could not acquire it.
It's under tight security.
In addition to being carefully guarded,
they have placed it in
a sea prism stone box.
Vexing!
But I vow to steal it all the same.
Just give me time.
Okay, no problem.
All right.
What are you doing here?
Couldn't help but notice
how hard you're working.
I wonder why.
Really want to hold all
those dumplings to yourself.
Don't you? Well,
I'm not giving you any get
your own caribou That was
awfully rude after all you
and I go way back don't we?
Wet-haired caribou of the caribou
pirates this despicable man left
Luffy beneath the Sabaody archipelago
He has quite the reputation
He attempted to raid the Sunny when
it was descending to Fishman Island,
but his plan failed and he was
captured by the Straw Hats.
When their adventure on Fishman Island was
coming to a close, they found it again,
trying to kidnap a group of mermaids.
Thanks to Luffy and Peckums,
his plan was foiled.
Later, after reaching the new world,
he wormed his way out of one
failed scheme after another.
For a time, it seemed that he
had found a new way of life,
that is, until Drake showed up suddenly!
Promptly defeated him and dragged
him off to the land of Wano.
Now he is forced to work at the excavation
labor camp in Udon alongside Luffy.
Be a pal,
mister—come on, help the needy!
needy
Surely you could share one
measly millet dumpling with me?
Earn it to yourself, then.
Just go away.
Not even an ounce of sympathy.
We're all cuffed with the C-prism stone.
They're supposed to weaken our power, but
not so much that we're unable to work.
I barely have the
strength to move anymore.
I don't give a crap. Try harder.
Man, why you gotta be like that?
Tell you what.
Give me some dumplings,
and I'll hinge for you.
I've been locked up in this
hellhole for a lot longer than you.
Do you want some insider info?
Huh?
So what you say? Sound good?
Just say the word. Ah!
Knock it off!
But I can tell what you're up to.
You want to break out of
here, isn't that right?
Let me help.
Go away!
You better stop slacking up!
That's right.
That guy was really strong.
He overpowered the three of us with ease.
I don't have time for this today.
If you'll recall, I was invited
to Shogun Orochi's banquet.
Contact Queen.
Let him take care of it.
He can send in some assassins.
That would cause an uproar.
what it did and your
point yes sir excuse
me the oiran is almost here shogun aruchi
excellent oh Komurasaki
today will be the day that
i finally make you mine